<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cairo Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ahmed_adel">Ahmed Adel</string>
    <string name="email">ahmedrabie7313@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="title_activity_aaaa">aaaa</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_place_detailes">place_detailes</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museame">egtian Museam contains thiusands of picies ofancient Egyptian history that will astonish your mind when you see it and there is a guide inside the useam that will explain for you all the information that you will need so you can gasp a look at the ancient history of egypt</string>
    <string name="mohamed_ali_detailed_info">The Great Mosque of Muhammad Ali Pasha or Alabaster Mosque (Arabic: مسجد محمد علي, Turkish: Mehmet Ali Paşa Camii) is a mosque situated in the Citadel of Cairo in Egypt and commissioned by Muhammad Ali Pasha between 1830 and 1848.

Situated on the summit of the citadel, this Ottoman mosque, the largest to be built in the first half of the 19th century, is, with its animated silhouette and twin minarets, the most visible mosque in Cairo.

The mosque was built in memory of Tusun Pasha, Muhammad Ali's oldest son, who died in 1816.

This mosque, along with the citadel, is one of the landmarks and tourist attractions of Cairo and is one of the first features to be seen when approaching the city any direction.</string>

    <string name="egyptian_museum">The Museum of Egyptian Antiquities, known commonly as the Egyptian Museum or Museum of Cairo, in Cairo, Egypt, is home to an extensive collection of ancient Egyptian antiquities. It has 120,000 items, with a representative amount on display, the remainder in storerooms. The edifice is one of the largest museums in the region. As of July 2017, the museum is open to the public.</string>
    <string name="el_suhimi_house">Bayt Al-Suhaymi ("House of Suhaymi") is an old Ottoman era house museum in Cairo, Egypt. It was originally built in 1648 by Abdel Wahab el Tablawy along the Darb al-Asfar, a very prestigious and expensive part of Medieval Cairo. In 1796 it was purchased by Sheikh Ahmed as-Suhaymi whose family held it for several subsequent generations. The Sheikh greatly extended the house from its original through incorporating neighbouring houses into its structure.

The house is built around a sahn in the centre of which there is a small garden with plants and palm trees. From here several of the fine mashrabiya windows in the house can be seen. Today the house is a museum which foreign visitors can tour for 35 Egyptian pounds (15 for students). Much of the marble floor work, wooden furniture, and ceiling decor is still intact</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabed_">Tabed_Activity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ssssssssssssss">ssssssssssssss</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="islamic_museum_title">Islamic Museum</string>
    <string name="islamic_museum_information">The Museum of Islamic Art, in Cairo, Egypt, is considered one of the greatest in the world.</string>
    <string name="islamic_museum_detaild_information">The Museum of Islamic Art, in Cairo, Egypt, is considered one of the greatest in the world, with its exceptional collection of rare woodwork and plaster artefacts, as well as metal, ceramic, glass, crystal, and textile objects of all periods, from all over the Islamic world.

In recent years, the museum has displayed about 4,500 artefacts in 25 Halls ,[1] but it houses more than 100,000 objects, with the remainder in storage. The collection includes rare manuscripts of the Qur\'an, with some calligraphy written in silver ink, on pages with elaborate borders.

The Museum has conducted archaeological excavations in the Fustat area and has organized a number of national and international exhibitions. The museum closed for renovations in 2003, and re-opened 8 years later, in August 2010.[1] The restoration cost nearly US$10 million</string>
    <string name="pyramids_of_giza">The Great Pyramid of Giza (also known as the Pyramid of Khufu or the Pyramid of Cheops) is the oldest and largest of the three pyramids in the Giza pyramid complex bordering what is now El Giza, Egypt. It is the oldest of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World, and the only one to remain largely intact.

Based on a mark in an interior chamber naming the work gang and a reference to the fourth dynasty Egyptian Pharaoh Khufu, Egyptologists believe that the pyramid was built as a tomb over a 10- to 20-year period concluding around 2560 BC. Initially at 146.5 metres (481 feet), the Great Pyramid was the tallest man-made structure in the world for more than 3,800 years. Originally, the Great Pyramid was covered by limestone casing stones that formed a smooth outer surface; what is seen today is the underlying core structure. Some of the casing stones that once covered the structure can still be seen around the base. There have been varying scientific and alternative theories about the Great Pyramid\'s construction techniques. Most accepted construction hypotheses are based on the idea that it was built by moving huge stones from a quarry and dragging and lifting them into place.There are three known chambers inside the Great Pyramid. The lowest chamber is cut into the bedrock upon which the pyramid was built and was unfinished. The so-called[1] Queen's Chamber and King's Chamber are higher up within the pyramid structure. The main part of the Giza complex is a set of buildings that included two mortuary temples in honour of Khufu (one close to the pyramid and one near the Nile), three smaller pyramids for Khufu's wives, an even smaller "satellite" pyramid, a raised causeway connecting the two temples, and small mastaba tombs surrounding the pyramid for nobles.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="koshary_eltahrear">Koshary el Tahrear</string>
    <string name="kushary_detailed">Kushari, also koshari (Egyptian Arabic: كشرى‎, [ˈkoʃæɾi]), is an Egyptian dish originally made in the 19th century, made of rice, macaroni, and lentils mixed together, topped with a spiced tomato sauce, and garlic vinegar, and garnished with chickpeas and crispy fried onions. A sprinkling of garlic juice, or garlic vinegar, and hot sauce are optional.</string>
    <string name="kabab_details">Kebabs (also kabobs or kababs) are various cooked meat dishes, with their origins in Middle Eastern cuisine. Many variants are popular throughout Asia, and around the world.

In Indian English[1] and in the languages of the Middle East, other parts of Asia, and the Muslim world, kebab is a broad term covering a wide variety of grilled meat dishes.[2] Although kebabs are often cooked on a skewer, many types of kebab are not.[3] Kebab dishes can consist of cut up or ground meat or seafood, sometimes with fruits and vegetables; cooked on a skewer over a fire, or like a hamburger on a grill, baked in a pan in an oven, or as a stew; and served with various accompaniments according to each recipe. The traditional meat for kebabs is most often mutton or lamb, but regional recipes may include beef, goat, chicken, fish, or more rarely due to religious prohibitions, pork.

In most majority English-speaking countries, two of the most prevalent and familiar kebab dishes are shish kebab and doner kebab. Either of these are often simply referred to as a "kebab" in English.

</string>
    <string name="flafel">doughnut or patty made from ground chickpeas, fava beans, or both. Falafel is a traditional Middle Eastern food, that most likely originated in Egypt.[2][3][4] It is commonly served in a pita, which acts as a pocket, or wrapped in a flatbread known as taboon; "falafel" also frequently refers to a wrapped sandwich that is prepared in this way. The falafel balls are topped with salads, pickled vegetables, hot sauce, and drizzled with tahini-based sauces. Falafel balls may also be eaten alone as a snack or served as part of a meze (assortment of appetizers).</string>
    <string name="ramsis">The Statue of Ramesses II is a 3,200-year-old figure of Ramesses II, depicting him standing. It was discovered in 1820 by Giovanni Battista Caviglia at the Great Temple of Ptah near Memphis, Egypt. It is made from red granite.

The statue was found broken in six pieces and earlier attempts at restoration failed. In 1955, Egyptian Prime Minister Gamal Abdel Nasser moved it to the large Bab Al-Hadid square in Cairo that was then renamed Ramses Square.[1] There the statue was restored to its full height of 11 meters and erected on a three metre pedestal at the edge of a fountain. It was stabilized by iron bars inside the body.

Over time Ramses Square turned out to be an unsuitable location, as the statue was exposed to corrosive pollution and constant vibration from traffic and subways. The Egyptian government decided to relocate it to a more appropriate location. At a temporary site on the Giza Plateau it will undergo restoration before being moved near the future Grand Egyptian Museum</string>
    <string name="dahshour">Dahshur[transliteration 1] (in English often called Dashur; Egyptian Arabic: دهشور‎ Dahšūr  pronounced [dɑhˈʃuːɾ]) is a royal necropolis located in the desert on the west bank of the Nile approximately 40 kilometres (25 mi) south of Cairo. It is known chiefly for several pyramids, two of which are among the oldest, largest and best preserved in Egypt, built from 2613–2589 BC.</string>
    <string name="al_azhar">Al-Azhar Mosque (Arabic: جامع الأزهر‎, Egyptian Arabic: الأزهر‎ Gām3` el-Azhar, "mosque of the most resplendent") is an Egyptian mosque in Islamic Cairo. Al-Mu\'izz li-Din Allah of the Fatimid dynasty commissioned its construction for the newly established capital city in 970. Its name is usually thought to allude to the Islamic prophet Muhammad\'s daughter Fatimah, a revered figure in Islam who was given the title az-Zahrār.It was the first mosque established in Cairo, a city that has since gained the nickname "the City of a Thousand Minarets</string>
    <string name="sultan_hassa_madrasah">The Mosque-Madrassa of Sultan Hassan is a massive mosque and madrassa located in the Old city of Cairo, it was built during the Mamluk Islamic era in Egypt. Its construction began 757 AH/1356 CE with work ending three years later "without even a single day of idleness".[1] At the time of construction the mosque was considered remarkable for its fantastic size and innovative architectural components. Commissioned by an-Nasir Hasan, a sultan of a short and relatively unimpressive profile, al-Maqrizi noted that within the mosque were several "wonders of construction".[1] The mosque was, for example, designed to include schools for all four of the Sunni schools of thought: Shafi'i, Maliki, Hanafi and Hanbali</string>
    <string name="al_hussin">he Al-Hussain Mosque is a mosque built in 1154 The mosque is located in Cairo, Egypt, near the Khan El-Khalili bazaar. It is considered to be one of the holiest Islamic sites in Egypt. The mosque was built on the cemetery of the Fatimid caliphs, though this was not known until the site\'s archaeological </string>
    <string name="feedpack">FeedBack</string>
    <string name="opens_at_9">opens at 9 am</string>
    <string name="koshary_onformation">one of the most famous Egyptian food ever</string>
    <string name="koshary_eltahreer__phone">tel:19719</string>
    <string name="koshary_eltahreer_website">http://koshary-eltahrir.com/</string>
    <string name="koshary_location">geo:29.979487, 31.134250</string>
    <string name="kabab_name">Kabab</string>
    <string name="kabab_info">Kebabs (also kabobs or kababs) are various cooked meat dishes, with their origins in Middle Eastern cuisine</string>
    <string name="kabab_location">geo:30.029080, 31.259514</string>
    <string name="kabab_pnone">tel: 0100 734 2507</string>
    <string name="kabab_websit"><![CDATA[https://www.elmenus.com/ar/cairo/search-%D9%85%D8%B4%D9%88%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA?delivery=1&isopen=0]]></string>
    <string name="flafel_name">Flafel</string>
    <string name="flafel_info">Falafel is a common food eaten in the Middle East.</string>
    <string name="flafel_location">geo: 30.052484, 31.262578\\n\" +  \"\\n,?z=18</string>
    <string name="flafel_phone">tel: 011 54265654</string>
    <string name="flafel_websit">https://www.facebook.com/s7emy.house/</string>
    <string name="al_azhar_mosqe_name">Al-Azhar Mosque</string>
    <string name="opens_all_the_time">opens all the time</string>
    <string name="al_azhar_info">Al-Azhar Mosque is an Egyptian mosque in Islamic Cairo.</string>
    <string name="al_azhar_location">geo:30.032562, 31.256203</string>
    <string name="al_azhar_phone">tel:45345354645</string>
    <string name="al_azhar_website">https://www.memphistours.com/Egypt/Egypt-Wikis/Cairo-Attractions/wiki/Al-Azhar-Mosque-Cairo</string>
    <string name="sultan_hassan_name">Sultan Hassan Madrasah</string>
    <string name="sultan_hassan_info">The Mosque-Madrassa of Sultan Hassan is a massive mosque and madrassa located in the Old city of Cairo</string>
    <string name="sultan_hassan_location">geo:30.029080, 31.259514</string>
    <string name="sultanhassan_phone">tel: 0100 734 2507</string>
    <string name="sultan_hassan_websit">http://www.touregypt.net/featurestories/hassanmosque.htm</string>
    <string name="el_hussin_name">Al-Hussein Mosque</string>
    <string name="el_hussin_info">The Al-Hussain Mosque is a mosque built in 1154 The mosque is located in Cairot.</string>
    <string name="el_hussin_location">geo: 30.048111, 31.262997</string>
    <string name="el_hussin_phone">tel: 011 54245465654</string>
    <string name="el_hussin_websit">https://www.memphistours.co.uk/Egypt/Egypt-Travel-Guide/Cairo-Attractions/wiki/Mosque-of-Saiyidna-Hussein</string>
    <string name="pyramids_name">Pyramids of Giza</string>
    <string name="pyramids_info">one of the 7 amazies of the world</string>
    <string name="pyramids_location">geo:29.979487, 31.134250</string>
    <string name="pyramids_phone">tel:02 257445694596\"</string>
    <string name="pyramids_websit">http://www.sca-egypt.org/eng/SITE_GIZA_MP.htm</string>
    <string name="mit_rahina_name">Mit Rahina Museum Colossus of Ramses II</string>
    <string name="mit_rahina_info">The Statue of Ramesses II is a 3,200-year-old figure of Ramesses II</string>
    <string name="mit_rahina_location">geo:29.29.795554, 31.246710</string>
    <string name="mit_rahina_phone">tel: 555555</string>
    <string name="mit_rahina_websit">https://www.lonelyplanet.com/egypt/saqqara-memphis-dahshur/attractions/mit-rahina/a/poi-sig/1427164/1330429</string>
    <string name="dahsour_name">Dahshur</string>
    <string name="dashour_info">An ancient pyramed made before the three famous pyrameds from around th 5 centireis which located in Dahshour village i Egypt</string>
    <string name="dahsour_location">geo: 30.052484, 31.262578</string>
    <string name="dahsour_phone">tel: 011 54265654</string>
    <string name="dahsour_website">https://www.facebook.com/s7emy.house/</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museame_name">Egyptian Museum Cairo</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museame_info">Tracing 5.000 years of ancient epyptian history</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museame_location">geo:30.047968, 31.233809</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museame_pjone">tel:02 25794596</string>
    <string name="egyptian_museame_website">http://www.antiquities.gov.eg/DefaultEn/Museum/Pages/MuseumDetails.aspx?MusCode=28#</string>
    <string name="mohamed_ali_name">Mohamed Ali Mosqe</string>
    <string name="mohamed_ali_info">Built in 18 centiries in the middle of Saladin casitle</string>
    <string name="mohamed_ali_location">geo:30.029080, 31.259514</string>
    <string name="mohamed_ali_phone">tel: 555555</string>
    <string name="mohamed_ali_websit">https://www.marefa.org/%D9%85%D8%B3%D8%AC%D8%AF_%D9%85%D8%AD%D9%85%D8%AF_%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%8A</string>
    <string name="el_suhimi_house_name">El Suhimi house</string>
    <string name="el_suhimi_house_info">An ancient house from the 5 centireis which located in Al mo\'es streat</string>
    <string name="el_suhimi_house_location">geo: 30.052484, 31.262578</string>
    <string name="el_suhimi_house_phone">tel: 011 54265654</string>
    <string name="el_suhimi_house_websit">https://www.facebook.com/s7emy.house/</string>
    <string name="islamic_museum_location">geo:30.045495, 31.252196</string>
    <string name="islamic_museum_phone">tel:02 23901520</string>
    <string name="sultan_hassan_name2">Sultan Hassan Madrasah</string>
    <item name="opens_at_9" type="id">opens at 9 ap</item>
</resources>
